Right. I know I got you with
that good packaging, but before you leave,
I need to
show you something. I'm James Smith.
I'm a three-times number one best-selling
author, and I'm good at sales and
marketing. Behind me,
three number one best-selling books.
We raised nearly $4 million for New Tonic
this year, valued at over $20
million. Yesterday,
we did 50,000 US dollars in a day.
And I'm here today to convince you to join
my business mentorship.
Now,
this could really badly backfire on me,
but if you look at the comments, there
are going to be people
that actually work with me inside giving
you real feedback.
They have the opportunity to completely
pull my pants down here, but let's see.
Once you're inside, I build courses.
And I know you've got the classic course
bro, I get it, but each one of these has a
problem that you face in mind.
Whether it's with content creation at the
top of the
funnel,
whether it's with creating lead magnets
that help you get email addresses
because you should have about 20% of every
single person that follows you's email
address. And at any point that you join,
you get lifetime access.
So about this time last year,
the Black Friday offer
was about 1,000 pounds.
It's now double that,
and I guarantee by next year it will be
well over double that
as well. But the Discord
is going to be the bit
that sets you apart.
I want you to think of the course as the
bit you go to to learn stuff, to get
questions. Then the questions
that you have, you come to the Discord.
Now,
we've got a thread here called Post Your
Wins.
Let's go up and have a look at some of the
ones recently.
Liv just hit 10,000 followers.
May not seem a massive deal,
but it's taken her
quite a long time. And to crack that,
I think it's really important for a
business.
Met her last weekend at the business
event. Now, you'll notice Ryan here.
We have this thing about when you join,
everyone gets set a challenge of posting
100 times in 100 days.
Not even 30 days into posting,
and my TikTok has gone from
nought to 15,000 followers,
over four million views
and averaging 20,000 to 40,000
per video. Amazing. Charles Ellen Price,
arguably one of the best and biggest
names in the jujitsu S&C,
just hit 200 members for his program.
Kevin having his first video hit 50,000 on
YouTube.
Lewis, 56 leads from one video. Now,
Catherine Sargent is going to be one
of my favorite ones.
If any of you follow me on Instagram,
you'll notice I shared
her to my story about a year ago saying
she deserves more followers.
And she just went viral two years into the
program, which can
seem like a really slow amount of time,
but she's grown her business.
She's now just getting the vanity
that she deserves. And look at this.
Imagine this for a ratio.
So her post has got her 667 people to
sign up to the email list because she's
using a chatbot.
Don't worry, there's a course on it.
At 267 likes.
She's getting almost three times the
amount of leads than she has likes.
Now, Thomas Menzies,
I want to show you this.
We've had to work quite hard.
Well, I don't say we, he's had to work.
I give the guidance.
I am not taking credit for anyone's
results. They achieve their own results.
I'm just the one that helps them.
Sometimes it's just turning up and saying,
"Mate,
that was shit.
This hook needs to be better.
Make it about them,
not about you," et cetera.
And he's just blown up recently.
Let's have a look at some of these stats.
12,000, 20,000, 20,000, 20,000,
1.9 million.
Look at this. "If you want some help,
comment SS or split squat." The guy had
a chatbot automation on a video
that got 1.9 million.
That's one of the things, right?
Some people say, "James,
should I start posting
content first, or do I need to wait?"
And I'm like, "Look,
eventually you're going
to have a post that goes ape shit.
And when that post goes ape shit,
we need to
have your ecosystem in order." We need to
have everything aligned so that you can
capture that data.
Because it's a very harsh reality going
viral and not getting
anything from it.
Getting a million views on a video
and not seeing any changes in
your Stripe account, it's just killer.
Gerald Lee, again,
saw him at the business event last week.
I actually had seen on his story,
because I follow him, that he
was in business
class. We're at the event. I said, "Hey,
mate, how was business class?
Was it your first time?" He's like,
"Yeah." He surprised his girlfriend.
She didn't even know.
He came from Singapore to the business
event, and I said to
him, "I would not have flown
that way to come see me." Again,
worked with him
one-to-one about a year ago.
Catherine Sargent at 15,000 followers.
I'm sure she's going to take off
and do a lot more.
Got people here having $17,000 days.
But some of the wins also
are just about hitting your first 1,000
subs.
And again,
if you look at Catherine Sargent's
progress here, she was turning up and
posting every day. Then boom.
Then it all kicks off.
If we get into some of these here,
you'll notice this is me in here all the
time,
giving people the directions of how their
landing pages need to go.
And do you know what? This is my pitch.
There is an offer to get a discount to my
business mentorship.
I'm probably going to take about 50.
I think there's 52 spaces left for the
rest of the year.
I am in here all the fucking time,
every single day emptying these
threads. There is no massive team.
We've got Cam down here, who actually was
in the mentorship, and he
was helping other people.
And I said, "Mate,
let me pay you for this." So he's got his
own thread.
But there are evenings I've got my laptop
out on the sofa, and I'm just so
invested in everyone's businesses here
that it's a fucking good deal.
And ultimately,
there's links in the description for free
stuff, but there's going
to be a link to my Black Friday offer.
And if you don't think that it's worth it,
then fuck you, because [laughs] I've
been working so hard,
not just helping these guys,
but learning the trade,
putting the hours in,
and getting really good at this.
The people beneath me,
there's a lot of people that
are selling advice that they
don't know.
They're giving advice on growing social
media.
They've got small accounts.
They're teaching you how to make money,
and they've
never made money. The people above me
are so fucking minted
that they just put you
in a team of random fucking people,
and they don't actually talk to you
themselves.
I'm in the valley of death, if anything,
right?
I'm rich enough to like the fucking finer
things in life, but I'm poor enough that
I'm still in here every day helping
fucking businesses for hours
and hours on end.
Until we sell New Tonic,
I've not got generational wealth.
So you'll find me in here.
I'll be in here later.
And if you don't fucking believe me,
read the fucking comments.
And as for how genius the packaging
was for this video, I actually saw it in
another video. And actually,
the very next course
that we're adding to the business
mentorship is a YouTube one.
And once we add that,
I'm probably going to put the
price up about $1,000.
Because I fucking can.
So you use that link or don't,
because at the end of the day,
just have a look at
that.
I've already made 1.9 million US dollars
this year from this.
So if you don't fucking join, honestly,
it's your loss. Right, virgins?
Use the Black Friday link or fuck off.
I'm only joking.
I'm going to keep putting out content for
free because I do love helping you guys.
And there's another key principle
that I have inside the business
mentorship.
I call it the fist bump effect.
If you can't be happy with 90% of people
not buying
your stuff,
you're not looking at content right.
Because you actually need people to not
buy your stuff to grow in videos and get
far and wide enough. And also,
if you're offended by me telling you to
fuck off,
you'd be an awful client anyway.
That's why it's banter. All right.
Double gun pose. You can tell
which arm I wank with.
There'll be a video here for you to watch
if you're not going to buy.
But don't watch this video. Fucking buy.
Because when this...
I can't wait to come back on here and go,
"Ha ha, motherfuckers.
Doors are closed." All right.
So I've had a coffee, how about you?